[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast
[Music]
with ourselves
50 episodes today i'm releasing my 50th
episode
of the junkyard love podcast and i just
wanted to do an intro for it i just
wanted to do
a summarization of what i've learned
from releasing 50 podcast episodes i've
had nearly 50 guests a couple
couple triple guests in a couple more
than once
i've already recorded the next six
episodes
um it's been quite a journey it's been
really cool
it's been one of the coolest things that
i've ever partaken honestly
to have such in-depth conversations and
really see so many different sides of
people and really just
pull their story out of them um in a way
that they're comfortable in a way that
that's their truth you know learning
about people and
learning how different we really truly
are you know i've had
rappers and poets and reiki healers
and life coaches and moms and carpenters
and electricians and bodybuilders and
um store owners and
entrepreneurs and creators and
construction workers and just
so many different types of people you
know and you really get to see below the
surface of what our
what our working title job is we really
get to experience each other from
another level we really get to
learn about each other on another level
i mean that's
that's been the biggest thing for me
with this with this podcast is
is the knowledge that you get from just
mining the people around you
just reaching out to people who you've
met or people that you find interesting
or people that intrigue you and just say
hey can you tell me part of your story
and behind that question there's just a
a a giant body of of
new knowledge a new perspective in new
ways to change your view on the world
there's new
at every turn with every new person that
you meet with every interaction that you
have
they all know something that you don't
and they can teach you something
that you never knew to ask they could
teach you what you don't know
that you didn't know there's so many
different
versions of ourselves that we bring to
the table there's so many different
parts of us that we've presented to the
world in different ways through
social media through person-to-person
interaction
you know our our work self our at home
self
our relationship self our
creative self there's different versions
of
of all of us and i think
i think learning about it and learning
about one another
just reminds us how much we really don't
know it just
more information is not always more
knowledge more wisdom right but
i think when you could really learn from
people's perspective and you can learn
from
what is their message what have they
seen what have they gone through and
and how could i take their lessons and
apply them to my own life how can i
mine the lessons and stories that they
tell to
pull out the best parts for other people
how can we
hear things that we've heard before said
in a different demeanor or a different
tone
and have them spark something within us
as individuals
i hope that what you guys have gotten
out of the first 50 episodes is
is even half as much as what i've gotten
you know the all these
wonderful fantastic people that have
agreed to come on the podcast
and agree to share a side of their story
and they've agreed to
really be so vulnerable and so really
put themselves out there
because they think that it will help
other people
because it does you sharing your story
helps other people in so many ways that
you can't understand you sharing what
you have learned so far
and sharing that you don't have it all
figured out
is a reminder to all of us that we we're
looking around on social media and in
person and all these things and we're
assuming that everyone
assumes they have it figured out but
nobody does and i think that's the
beauty of all of it when you learn
from people from their first hand
experience and you just
create room for them to speak and and
say something from within them sometimes
they didn't even know they were gonna
say
you really get to see people with new
eyes
we're always telling stories we've been
telling stories we've been
sitting around campfires for years and
years and years for many years as
a human civilization we've always
relayed stories and
and you heard about this thing through
this person and now we have different
ways of relaying stories we have
we have the bite size stories we have
videos we have
movies we have podcasts we have all
these things and
it just seems so interesting that
long-form podcasts come back around and
they can really dig out some interest in
us
we think that everything is so
bite-sized and sure it is
sure that's how we get our information
but how do we get
what does it have to say what does it
have to do
when you see so many numbers when you
see so many people listening to two
three hour four hour long conversations
and having value from it
i think that says something i think it
says that that we're a bit disconnected
and i think when we can as individuals
find
places to connect bridges within each
other's personalities within
conversation we can find
bridges to one another to one another's
truest self
and we can meet there we could have the
conversation there we're so divided
right now there's a pandemic going on
when i first started this podcast i
certainly didn't plan there being a
pandemic i
you know the first couple of months
after it happened i was like i don't
know what what do i do
what do i have people talk about their
dreams and their new business and their
new entrepreneur goals and
um try to fake hope on here i didn't
know what to do but i just kept plugging
along and i kept doing it because
this podcast is important to me and i
think that it's important to other
people and i want it to be important to
other people
i think that when you put your
importance into something other people
see that they're like yeah
all right all right it's okay to make
things important it's okay to put my
time and energy into something that only
i see
and maybe other people don't see or
experience in the way that i do
it's okay i think
i've learned so much you know this
pandemic
continuing the podcast through it
this this whole thing has been such a
journey for me you know listeners are
listeners of the podcast are are right
with me on my journey you know i have i
record episodes where i'm feeling
depressed i have guests over when my
adhd is through the roof and i can't
seem to focus i have
i listen to myself with these different
versions of myself and then when i
re-edit it i'm
i have to deal with with my own
self-deprecation i have to deal with my
own like self-hate thoughts and have to
watch them and i have to say oh
you're not going to edit that out you're
not going to edit that part where you're
rambling because that's who you are and
that's okay and it's okay to not be
perfect with your words all the time
and i get to see people in different
perspectives and i get to see people in
different
versions and different characters of
their own character
you know we're always trying to explain
ourselves in one post
in one paragraph in one caption
in one four hour long conversation well
you couldn't if you tried
and i hope what my guests and my
listeners have gotten
out of this first 50 episodes are are
that
nobody's perfect really that
that nobody's perfect that
it's okay to accept the imperfectness of
everyone and realize that you can learn
from
each individual person everyone's
perception everyone's perspective
of their reality is filled with gold
flakes
for yours it's filled with with
little ideas and little inspirations
and little ways to believe in yourself
it's each
interaction with every person that you
have each conversation
there's power there everyone knows
something you don't and you could mine
that
and you could just speak with them and
just leave open room to talk
just listen
i think
what i've learned about the podcast is
certainly to go easy on myself editing
all the episodes i really listen to how
much
i mean to myself i judge myself for not
being the best at whatever i judge
myself for not being
ellen degeneres level podcast host i
judge myself for not being as good as
dr phil or oprah with my inquisitive
questions
i i judge myself in all of these ways
but
when i finish the episodes when i post
them i'm always like all right
i've let that go i've listened to that
part i didn't edit it out i didn't try
to make myself
sound more exact i didn't edit out the
pauses i didn't edit out the skips
i didn't edit out the parts where the
guest even said hey you could take that
part out because
blah blah blah you know we all have our
own insecurities we all have our own
imperfections we all have all these
things that only we judge but
realistically
the people on the other side the people
who are listening the people who are
watching you
they just see you as as you and when we
really give each other space to
be you to experience
from our perfectly imperfect
individual lens really
real beauty is born there um
i think that
the the hero's journey the
healing journey that everybody is is
joining me on
is
every few minutes there's new knowledge
to mine every
every couple minutes every few sentences
to me
with this podcast is like oh man that's
that's a heater
when someone says something that's a
there's different
types of people saying different types
of things
but when you're able to say like what
what does that mean to me what does that
mean to my life what could i learn from
that
what are they teaching me right now or
even
look at this beautiful person expressing
themselves what is the
the true art of this being in front of
me expressing
and you could just feel that
i plan to keep going with the podcasts i
enjoy it
i love it it challenges me it pushes me
it takes up
a crazy amount of my time and then
returns a crazy amount of my time with
just fulfillment
it opens up doors that i never expected
it gets me to have conversations on
levels with people that i never thought
that i would have
the podcast has been a true blessing for
me
um and i'm so excited that i started it
so
what i hope that you guys have gotten
from these first 50 episodes is really
just
believe in your damn self and just try
it if you have a podcast if you want to
start a podcast if you have a
if you want to start being a rapper if
you want to start being a poet if you
want to open your own business if you
want to start a family if you want to do
these things and you're on the edge and
you're waiting for someone to give you
permission here's your permission right
now
do that thing that's yelling at you that
only you can do
believe in yourself i'll see you guys
the next
50 episodes tomorrow
now here's episode 50 with jordan now
tsugawa
i hope you enjoy the show it's very
uplifting
yeah i do it as my um citrus i have like
it's like orange
tangerine lemon and something else i
think
and that's kind of my in the morning
when i'm making my coffee it's like my
get things going get my brain turned on
it's my like focus let's work
sort of scent i love that it's
interesting because
like a lot of your session was focusing
on those areas
where those scents align with those
chakras interesting
okay so get pull this thing a little bit
closer to you if you could yeah of
course
is that better no i don't know that's
better okay
and i could always just beef it up and
post as long as i get a good signal from
you so we just did
my first reiki session yeah and i feel
uh it's hard to describe it's like
equanimity
yeah um so i i don't want to
i have i mean i'll put my foot in my
mouth all day i don't mind but
i would like to leave you the room to
explain
and um and just teach me what's what's
going on what just happened
okay so basically i set up my table in
his space
and we just did like a basic 30 minute
reiki session
for those of you who've never heard of
reiki which a lot of you probably
haven't it's an
ancient japanese style technique for
stress reduction and relaxation
that's like the wikipedia that's a big
dictionary
but really what i'm doing is i'm
allowing
the universal energy to flow through me
onto whatever i'm like
putting my energy into but it's not my
energy it's like the universe's
so that's a difference with like another
energy worker that wasn't reiki they're
using their own energy and after they
could feel drained
but since i'm using the universe's
energy i'm getting a session too
so like you feel good i feel good like
every time i'm giving a session like
seriously i'm getting it too so it's
really um like an addicting thing for me
since i've started because
when you have this universal energy
flowing through you
it's like enlightening yeah it really is
and it's so hard to put into words
it's weird for me to feel good i guess
is the words it's weird for me to not
have anxiety or to be stressed or to be
concerned
with other people around me and to just
be floating through the world
navigating around just being me
and reiki has opened this pathway not
only for myself but for people who leave
my table to just
feel like they can be themselves and
that's like my intention behind it it's
healing at the energetic level
um it's really showing people that you
have the power to heal yourself
i'm i'm not a healer i'm i mean i am but
i'm teaching you how to heal yourself
basically like you leave my table and
you have to keep doing the work but
reiki hopefully inspires that maybe it's
unlocking parts of your brain that
you didn't even know you had or you
start getting ideas you're like well
i've never thought like this before
and you can't blame it all on reiki
people that leave my table
usually do feel better about themselves
they usually do feel lighter they feel
more energy
i don't know if you felt it but like you
were twitching a lot
like during your session like energy was
flowing through you i could feel it
it wasn't even like oh like i don't even
know
i could i literally physically could
feel like your feet
like twitching in my hands yeah i don't
know if you could feel that or not
yeah i mean kind of it's like a i was
really trying to concentrate on my
breath and trying to not
not think about twitching like if i felt
something i was like okay it's okay
jay told me it's gonna be like that's
gonna happen yeah so i was just trying
to like
get back to my breath and try to you
know pre my presence get back to
being here um but yeah i definitely did
feel like
like vibrations and twitches and um
yeah since there was also a moment where
you had moved away from my feet and it
took me
20 seconds to realize your hands weren't
on my feet anymore like it felt like you
were
your hands were still on my feet so that
was an interesting thing yeah
so having you um someone mentioned my
friend kaden told me this like where
you cut like a part of a flower off and
energetically that part is still there
you know you might not physically see it
but the plant still thinks it has that
limb
so if you were to like look at it at an
energetic level you would still see like
the part that you cut off for a while
so i feel like with reiki my physical
hands
might not be in that spot but the energy
that i just admitted from the universe
is still there
so that's why you can feel it still so
like sometimes people will be like i
felt like there's a hundred hands all
over my body
well that's just because like the
universal energy you're open to it
that's the experience you needed to feel
that's what you needed to feel to feel
good everyone's experience is so
different
so it's it's weird you said 100 hands i
literally
so there was a couple things that came
up
and it's hard to know if i
it's hard to decipher if i felt
from me it was the the what was louder
than the actual
feeling of multiple hands was the term a
thousand hands actually
it came in my head multiple times that's
interesting
yeah not not a hundred and again you
know that could just be a thought that
like
you know made itself but
um it's probably for those of you who
who are listening it's hard to kind of
explain like how you feel after your
first energy session because your body
is like feeling energy it's never maybe
felt
so a lot it's probably like i probably
put jake on the spot because i give him
this amazing energetic relaxation
almost like blissful
and calm and um when then you want to
try to talk about it it's kind of hard
to experience
explain your experience that's why i
wanted to kind of have this like raw
explanation and to just to just show
that
energy work is truly like all i
it is half an hour and the impact that
one half hour can have on your life is
life-changing my reiki sessions changed
my life
i've had like a few and i my first one i
was like i want to do this
i want to make people feel like this the
fact that i can put my hands on top of
your head and
like see your ideas and allow spirit to
show you your ideas is beautiful to me
i literally wrote down like a thing that
the universe like wants me to tell you
so it's so cool like working with people
because not only am i
like using reiki but i'm gonna i'm a
channel so a beautiful thing about reiki
is i can get
guides can come through messages can
come through
blocks that can come through and it's
really your soul talking to my higher
self which
i'm catching and allowing to hear it
because you're giving me that space
you're you're trusting me to be in your
energy so i can see what's in it
and i can hear it so one of my gifts is
i can't like see auras
but i could ask what color your aura is
and someone would tell me
right if that makes sense so i'm more of
like
images come into my head like i can
that's why i'm really good at
manifesting that's why visual
visualization is so important for me
because
i'm always tapping into the future or
no future i'm tapping into now but i'm
able to see
like what maybe you want like your
higher self
and then i'm getting visions of it and
then i'm able to like
show you what maybe you can't see but
it's in your energy
because you're what you want is stored
in your auric field
so that's why you attract people that
are gonna give you that or you track
situations that you're gonna get because
whether you
subconscious unconsciously know what you
really want your deepest desires are in
your auric field
and if you honor them then you're gonna
start
like energetically aligning with these
situations
like you're getting energy work now
because that's where you're at in your
spiritual journey it's a huge step
to believe in it i mean think about
three years ago like where people were
where you were where i was i mean i i
literally remember i was thinking about
this morning
i would um i would literally and it
wasn't
that i actually thought about it
intricately it wasn't that i was
actually intelligible about my opinion
right it was just i didn't know anything
about it so it's easier to make fun of i
would make fun of people with the rocks
three years ago like and not i'm i'm not
i've never been like a mean guy like i'm
not like really making fun but i would
throw my jabs just because it's
something that i didn't know about
um and now yeah it's just like something
like like before the session i was like
i'm ready for this i trust you i'm i was
looking forward to this
i was uh yeah it was it was really cool
it's so
it's funny you know life is is
the way that we see reality is always
trying to
decipher feelings and like the images in
our heads or
whatever you know words in your heads
however people think we're always trying
to
that's our reality but we're trying to
decipher it in words we're trying to
break it down and make it make sense in
words and in words
words are not enough to describe
um you know feelings in in
in profound like like there's just
words are the best tools we have but
they're not completely
uh fully rounded like you can't explain
exactly you can kind of trip around it
and it's enough to where like maybe
it'll catch interest and maybe it'll
um allow people to be like oh okay that
kind of makes more sense than it did at
least
but yeah that's that's how i feel with
reiki and it's one of those things where
i haven't had any questions anyone
questioned me yet
i'm sure people are underneath the
surface but
i mean to me energy is everything
i am an energetic being having a human
experience an infinite being having a
human experience i have a physical
vessel that allows me to navigate
through the world
but what's moving that vessel yeah my
heart my muscle but what's telling it to
do that or like what's
where are my ideas coming from you know
my higher self right is my higher self
inside is it up above is it in space
is it in heaven is it where do like
where does it come from you know what i
mean is our soul infinite
are all our souls like energetically
individual
and we're like navigating around on our
own i think we're all like
i feel like we're just each individual
almost like
neurons in someone's mind and that's why
like like things
are attracting and it's crazy because
there's more neurons in our body than
there are people on the planet
there's 10 billion neurons in our body
there's what seven seven and a half
billion so there's more
neurons inside of us so then think of us
as a unit moving around something bigger
because like then that makes you think
that you are small but then it makes you
think how important it is to keep your
personal energetic frequency high
because we are working as a unit
right it really does make a difference
and when i um when i say my mission is
to spread love and light
it really is because each person that i
can
help elevate their frequency we're
helping the whole planet it's really so
simple
it's so simple like we elevate each
other like having these conversations
having these energy sessions
you are in control of your frequency
that is your personal job on this planet
is to elevate your frequency i don't
care who you are
every single one that's listening it is
your personal responsibility to make
sure your frequency is high
i agree and when you live like that the
experiences that the universe gives you
are just i can't believe the experiences
i've had
because it's like i'm giving so much to
the planet like i'm thinking about the
planet all the time
every single day i'm thinking about what
we live on what's
clothing me what's feeding me where's my
water coming from what's keeping us
alive is this planet
so something that i'm very passionate
about is the planet
and i know a lot of us aren't there yet
in our spiritual process but when you
start to reconnect with
why we're here your whole life starts to
change
it's it's interesting that there's
there's different ways of coming to it
but like a lot of
a lot of stuff when it comes to like
self-healing or spirituality
or um anything in this realm it all ends
up like
reminding you in some way of like we are
one
you know it's like like you know i do
um i've been meditating for a couple
years now
and a lot of times it's just like a
reminder almost sometimes without even
trying to make it be it's a reminder
like i'll realize afterwards i'm like
okay i just kind of like reconnected to
that reminder that like this is all
one like who am i without the trees who
is my you know we we separate everything
to quantify it we separate
you know our inner workings like our our
heart and our lungs and our all these
things
in there that's how we're able to to
conceptualize like
what they're used for specifically and
how we can repair them
but we don't we kind of almost forget to
like reattach them like your lungs
are nothing without your heart your
heart is nothing without your vessels
like it's all one
and you could look at the earth in the
same sense you know like we wouldn't be
breathing it wasn't for trees
and to connect to that um i encourage
you to like
go outside and name some of the plants
in your yard
you even know who you're coexisting with
and that's something
and i'm not trying to put anyone down
because i just started doing this like
well what are these natural things that
are growing around like see to me i had
this realization two days ago
we have so many dandelions well i bet
like we all have maybe some
kidney issues i mean we all love coffee
we probably all drink too much coffee
well dandelion root helps with that it
helps balance out these coffee drinkers
because it helps with your kidneys
so medicine is all around us it's not
random that we have certain things
growing
like saint john's wort is growing in my
front yard st john's is like the best
thing for anxiety and depression and
it's literally a weed in my yard
thank you universe doesn't it help does
it help with inflammation at all too
probably i i feel it does nobody quote
me on that but i think it does
it probably i mean maybe inflammation of
your nerves because it helps with like
anxiety and depression but it's like if
you look around you
earth is always trying to help you heal
tune into that um i think the biggest
thing for me
is i believe in my heart that depression
is truly a disconnect from your
surroundings
and i think we talked about that in the
last episode because it's such a big
theme for me
i i wake up every morning i walk around
barefoot
i walk into my garden i eat what i grew
that's the first thing i put into my
body is something that i grew
i drink copper water um i like i try to
move
i've been really into like moving and
not moving in a structured way for me
you know i've um i haven't worked been
working out as much as i like
but i'm moving my body in how i want to
move it and not like
you know insanity or like lifting like i
used to think that was how i needed to
move or i need to be
moving in ways that other people are
moving i need to go to yoga class but
for me movement is like dancing
and like being more like energetically
in tune with my body
yeah i'm really with you on that i try
to um
especially if i'm if i catch myself
being in like a mopey mood or like a man
maybe it's not the best day today that's
okay
or whatever i'll put on like after i've
done my
my routine and i've got my day ready
i've meditated um and then it's like
okay it's time to work it's time to
create
i'll put on like there's a couple songs
that i'll put on and i'll purposely take
my shoes off
and i'll the intention with that is to
just dance around down here and it's
this like don't try to dance
don't try to you know don't try to do
anything anybody else is doing just try
to like
you almost you know the the truth of
dancing
is is getting out of the way so your
soul can move your body around right
yeah you know
it's and i think i think that when
people can do that and it's not an easy
thing to like
i think in today's modern age
everything's so like coordinated and
we your podcast just talked about that
like your individual one where like it's
so
society has made it normal to not move
yeah
it's like don't move around weird people
will look at you yeah
like imagine if you're if you're sitting
there on a bus and then all of a sudden
you start just going
and moving your eyes around and moving
your face around people will be like oh
my god that person's about to lose their
mind
they're gonna they're gonna go crazy
right now or they're gonna we
but it's like what what why is it okay
for us
why is it more socially accepted for us
to like try our best to never move our
eyes and try to like
keep our eyes on our phones all the time
because they want us to be
the sheep that's very true they want you
to fit in they want you to conform
um i don't i don't want to talk about it
but with the mask it's like no one wants
to wear it but yet we are explain this
to me
no one wants no one everyone i talk to
they're like don't agree with it but yet
we just do it
it's like we're when the government is
doing
i'm not trying to be like conspiracists
but
the word mask alone to me
is like not allowing your light to come
through so i think of it as a spiritual
level
making everyone and i was talking to a
kindergarten teacher
my mom was and how she communicates with
her kids through facial features but
kids at school are gonna be wearing
masks
oh yeah that's different what kind of
world our little five-year-olds
are wearing masks and that's normal
so we're changing we're really
conforming now
like it's even it's like i can't you
know what i mean
imagine like just envision like pledge
of allegiance to the flag with mask on
and you walk into that kind of class and
there's like five-year-olds like
i mean it's kind of weird because if you
really think like
we're such a such a ritualistic species
really like we you know
prayer in mudras and and and um
you know our meditations like we've
always all of our societies
through human culture from what we've
like read and uncovered and try to
decipher
they've always had some sort of like
this is the first time
these last couple hundred years of the
first time that we really had a society
that's completely rant on like on no
like higher god like there's no like
bigger than us thing like we're just
egos just maxing out
running around i think that um
like talking about the mask it's like i
i feel like
every time i start talking about um like
the race or like the race thing or masks
or
control or social media or all this
stuff like the more i learn about it the
more i like see how we're all reacting
to it the more i like
the more i i see how
it just seems like all these things are
so vastly connected
like yeah like it's really is
i mean whether you're a spiritual person
or not i feel like the uncovering the
unmasking the
awakening of the whole world right now
is just coming through in so many
different aspects like so many different
types of people are waking up and just
i think a lot of people are really
forced to uh i mean we have like a
traumatized society and i think a lot of
people are very forced to deal with
their traumas right now
and um i don't know what what do you
think about
the it's hard to like quantify but what
do you think about the world right now
like
do you feel similarities do you feel
that like
what we're going through is scary and
it's tough but like in a couple years
we're going to be able to
like we had to go through that or i
don't feel fear at all
really i haven't felt fear since one day
since this virus has happened
that's great um i think part of that is
who i surround myself with
my friends don't aren't scared of it um
i think it's not watching
media i think it's not being on facebook
reading fake articles i think
it's not allowing people to talk about
it in a fearful way
um because if you think about it this
has been planned this has been
talked about all even astrology has seen
this so my friend's astrologer and
um she's talked about how like in the
70s when the riots were
you know the 70s known for like the
rioting that's happening now the planets
were in the same
way in space so we're re-learning a
lesson a new generation is relearning
what a lesson our aunt like our elders
have learned but the virus thing
it's all planned it corona crown
it so many spirit no one's super
spiritual not that you have to be
spiritual to think this way
but a lot of people that i surround
myself with and that who i get my
information
from has not been scared this has been
planned
this is a like it's almost like the
light is winning
and this is like the darkness is last
thing to like grab on to any form of
control that there
is and to really um
but what it's actually doing is it's
bringing us closer together because
we're all like you
yeah who are you and it's really i love
um it's bringing us back to our roots
like more people want to learn about
gardening more people don't want to have
their babies at hospitals more people
are like doctors aren't always right
more people are questioning the
government for the first time
thank you a lot of people are seeing
that what we've been taught
something that i've known for a long
time it's all false
you know what what do who why do you
believe the news to be true
the news is all the same person every
single
different fox cnn emmet whatever they
are nbc
i don't even know them all i've seen
them all up on there with like 12 of
them they're all saying the same script
it's all fed to you to be fearful
if you're fearful they're controlling
you if you step into your power and you
know you
can't get sick if you feel that in your
bones i've never really been sick but if
you've
other than hungover but if you feel it
i'm not disregarding medicine but i'm
just saying like
when you're scared of something you're
attracting that to you fear
is that the lowest energy on the
energetic spectrum
if that's your fearful fearful things
are going to happen for you
it's your mindset this is a thing two
years ago i couldn't sit in a dark room
i would be like deem it like weird like
i would be scared now i'm like
there's nothing to be scared about
darkness is just the absence of light
wait actually let's sidestep what what
is that uh
so like i would have things where okay
so for example
even down here i'm go it's time to go to
bed it's four or five in the morning for
me
um i walk upstairs and then like the
light turns off behind me i would speed
walk
like through my laundry room and but i
don't have that anymore i feel like once
i started
doing a lot of my spiritual work i i
didn't realize
how many years i actually had like a
fear of the dark and i don't think it
was actually the dark it was just like a
reaction to
i don't know something primal yeah i
think it's like a pr
the amygdala like you're trying it's
like that primal thing too that people
are chasing us
but that's also fearful energy you know
you realize like
you're safe right um i think something
too though that a lot of us don't think
about is we
are so powerful our minds
are so powerful we create our life
you want to suffer you're going to
suffer i'm straight up like the
time why is this happening to me because
i want to be having this kind of shitty
experience right now for some reason
and to just you know i still go through
experiences but now i'm just like okay
what is here to learn like i was just
talking like what is the lesson
here because nothing is random every
single experience you can have can be
beautiful if you look at it like that
destruction is beautiful straight up
like tearing layers of who i thought i
was is hard but it's like allowing me to
be the person i'm always meant to be
you know what i mean and we're so scared
to like rip off these
labels right and it's like rip them off
like who are you who do you really want
to be and are you embodying that
why not like you said that you don't see
yourself as an artist and that's
so crazy to me like look at your space
you literally have art written on the
wall
like it's crazy to me that we don't see
who we really are
that is just crazy to me i mean
comparison is the thief of joy
there's a lot of that but it's a it it
it's
it's so crazy that our society runs
from a a place of
it being so difficult to step into who
we really are like like really just
think how simple it is like
so many people aren't doing what they
really want to be doing like they aren't
feeling fulfilled in what they're doing
um it's just crazy do you want to um i
want to
go back to my session do would you like
to share some of that or
yeah so some things that came up for you
is just like
what's holding you back from being the
best version of yourself
okay um why don't you like produce
more like music and sound because people
love it
i remember my experience i remember
every single set you've played that i've
been to
as like a great experience and everyone
around me too
like i remember everything i was drunk
but i remember like my experience
being there um because like
you might not see yourself as this way
but like shamans produce
music like creating experience through
sound allowing
when you are creating music i'm sure you
already know this because you're an
artist but the way
i love it is because everyone's
vibrating at the same vibration
you're literally changing the vibration
of hundreds of people with sound
you can choose to raise it so it's like
what's holding you back from doing those
things because i feel like that's what
you're
good at right um what are your limiting
beliefs you have on yourself
why don't you see yourself as an artist
like kind of just ask you that
but just like really thinking like
what's holding you back
like what limiting what is making
you like not see that you can do all
these things even though you're
literally doing it
yeah that's funny
and those are questions that spirit asks
so when spirit asks questions it's very
like cut throat but it's like
to the point because it's so simple you
know we over complicate it i do all the
work
obviously well like you still don't even
see who you really are you're not doing
enough work
because i see myself not all the time
and to see yourself as not being
egotistical it's actually the opposite
because i'm seeing my light i'm not
seeing my ego
you know what i mean i'm not seeing
everything i've accomplished i'm seeing
like who i am as an energetic being
and it's just infinite and it's just
love
and it is like me just being me is
allowing other people to just be them
and that's what i want to do
i want to just continue to show up and
be authentic and to continue
channeling things for people to enjoy
listening to to continue expanding minds
um but everyone can get here it's not
like it's just me
it's just a frequency that i'm vibing at
other people can tune up
this is for everyone to access it's not
just for me
it's for everyone and that's why i'm
like we can all be here yeah
i'm not a millionaire i don't have a lot
of money right now but i know that
i will and i do like if you manifest it
you know it's not all about money
you know that's something that i've been
working through a lot is like feeling
deserving of money
feeling that my spiritual gifts will
bring me money
trusting that what i want to do will
bring me money and that's a lot of
people's what's holding them back from
being what they really want to do is
they don't think it's worth anything
right yeah i think we we quantify if
it's worth our time
is it worth your time well does it make
you money no man don't do it
like that's that's how that's a limiting
belief yeah that's not great
it's crazy it's
it's so interesting i had oh so so
during our session
i also had like a
it's weird i i i'm half
it's funny too i'm also in just this
like super chill state i feel like yeah
that's what ricky does it makes you
super old
i'm soft for sure um i
so so i had this like time because
towards the beginning i actually
i felt um i had tears come out of my
eyes
and during that time it was actually
like a
i don't know okay so in my head i
actually remembered this time like
i don't know six years ago um where i
was at the ape caves
with a couple friends and we were
walking through and and we like stumbled
across towards the end
like these dudes uh with like an old
book
and candles and they were doing
something that felt weird and like a
weird vibe
um like it didn't make me comfortable
like
but it was so interesting like that that
moment
came up like like during tears like
i don't know if okay and so here's and
i'm not saying that i know this for sure
but i think back then
my like very quick small example of what
they were doing was like oh yeah they're
doing something like satanic stuff
like that are you fearful yeah and so
but
but really what if he was just like
lighting candles and like honoring the
earth
literally he could yeah it could have
been the nicest guy but we just walked
by with like this so
like weird like but he triggered you and
that's what he's supposed to do
and he remember that experience yeah it
was just so weird that that came up like
i haven't thought about that forever
it is weird like you know it's this is
not true but it's crazy because i'm like
what if that was like a future version
of yourself and you had no idea and only
you remember that that's
where my mind goes because like why do
you remember it i was thinking about
that when i was getting a reiki i'm like
memories are so weird they're like keys
to doors in our pathway of enlightenment
because why do you hold on to certain
memories why are they locked down
some are open some aren't you never
think about some you think about a lot
all the time and i think they're there
to guide you because we based so much
our life on our own experience
right but when you're remembering
something like that
it just kind of shows you kind of to me
it shows you your growth
because now if you saw that you would
probably ask asking what he's doing
stop by see what's up definitely but
that's showing you
spirit was showing you your growth hmm
it's interesting too when it comes to
memories
because you know something even like
like
like working through like a traumatic
childhood or something
like you you're able to take memories
that you didn't want to deal with before
but then
you open them back up and you see them
in a different light like it's still the
same memory
right but you you know you're able to
you to ask yourself like what okay what
really happened
what was my interpretation of it what
does that mean to me now
as a 28 year old 27 like whatever it is
like it's funny because the memories
stay the same
like the the past stays the same but
then you get to places
later on in your life where you change
and you're able to look back at old
memories that you
you know defined in such a such an
obtuse way
when you see it in a completely new
light yeah an exercise that i love
doing is going back to your memories and
changing how you would respond
and how you'd react and actually change
your current reality so you could go
back to that memory and talk to that
person you know
anything is possible don't let your mind
be like i can't go in the past
yes you can i do a lot of healing where
i go
back to whatever age i'm at and then
i'll give myself a hug at that age
if it's seven if it's 5 if it's 12 if
it's 16 if it's 21
whatever it is and i'm just letting that
person
know from the future that it's okay
you're it's all right you are loved you
are worthy
and in a crazy way it heals the present
because you're healing your past
because your past is happening now your
future is happening now your presence
happening now everything's happening now
right who knows if this is even
the present it's just what our mind is
thinking but i can go in the future like
this
i can go in the past like that is it
happening for me in that moment it
is so if you choose to go in the past
usually that causes depression
that's what we do we get stuck yep stuck
depression can't move can't change
because you're in the past no wonder you
can't change you're not in the
place to change you have anxiety you're
in the future
all the possibilities oh my gosh if i
did that's anxiety
when you choose to just be in the
present moment you don't feel
at least for me i don't feel those
things so when i can recognize that i'm
feeling low
when i recognize i'm being more manic i
can recognize that i'm not being present
and if you live your life in the past
and in the future the whole time are you
even living your life
right that's that's a huge one
i that that's the thing i love i try to
push that too it's like
depression you're thinking about the
past aren't you anxiety
you're anxious about the future aren't
you which means you're not here
no you're not concentrating on your five
senses you're not trying to get grounded
but it's it's
it's uh i gotta use different vocabulary
it's crazy i say that a lot
um i think that
there's a lot of this stuff that
quantifies and it stacks on each other
and that's something that is hard to
like you just have to trust you just
have to have the faith
but the more so for me the more that i
practice my meditation
the more that i i read my books on
meditation i listen to lectures on
meditation
um i learn different types different
teachers all these things
you're the teacher yeah yeah yeah see so
i'm like learning i'm almost like
sharpening my my own tool kit and
building my own tool bag in that same
way yeah because where will you be in
ten years
yeah you'll be leading meditation
retreats you don't even know it
there's a reason you're drawn to that's
something i'm not trying to cut you off
but spirit just like came through
there's a reason you're interested in
certain things and when you start
learning about something and you can't
stop
because you're learning it because
you're going to be teaching it so we
each are interested in certain topics
that are going to benefit the whole
planet and
they're all different topics right like
i'm interested in alternative healing
well i want to open a well i'm going to
open a wellness center
makes sense why am i connected to all
these different healers because they're
going to be there it's going to be a
coexisting place everyone wants
this center everyone in the world wants
a wellness center where we can just be
and heal it's not it's a universal thing
and the reason i feel like you're so
into all these things is because you
might be the teacher you might be coming
up with the meditation tracks i'm
listening to on youtube you might be the
best in the world that you don't even
know it
so there's a reason that you're super
drawn to it it's not random
either you know we can be like oh i'm
really into it because it's helping me
but
you have the ability to help others
through your experiences especially by
talking about it with other people
yeah i mean i i i stumble into it by
like helping myself like originally
like just like dude i want to not be
depressed anymore right and then over
the months and
in the years like it ends up you just
inevitably open a door to spirituality
like that was not what i was aiming for
it was just like like
so you just start like fumbling into
these things and it's
uh yeah it's crazy because i love
crazy to want to feel the want to be
here and that's straight up a fact for
me
it's crazy to want to be here on the
planet
like i'm not kidding like that's not
trying to be suicidal in any way
but i for most of my life did not want
to be here and it's not like
oh like i hate my life kind of thing i
was like i just don't vibe with a lot of
people here i don't vibe with a lot of
morals i don't vibe with the suffering i
don't vibe with how we're
poisoned i don't vibe with the societal
functioning norms of how people choose
to live their lives i don't vibe with a
lot of people
i can vibe but like my morals are just
so
different than so much of the planet
it's really uncomfortable for me to be
here especially being a starseed
i'm not from here so it is uncomfortable
for me to be
here and i think a lot of starseeds that
don't know their starseeds
don't usually want to be here yeah you
know we like signed up and we forgot
we're like i don't know my gifts help me
what am i doing here i forgot why i'm
here
it's it's getting stuck in this life is
happening to you not for you
exactly and then shifting your mindset
and then honoring that
you're here to change the frequency of
the whole planet it's like oh okay cool
i can do that
yeah now i know why i'm here and once
you start knowing why you're here and
embodying that you can maneuver better
and you can utilize your time be like
it's a gift to be on this planet
so many souls want to be on this planet
you think 7 billion is it
there's so many souls it's infinite so
many people want to be
this planet is beautiful straight up
there's not a lot of planets that look
like earth
there's not we haven't found any that's
what i'm saying like we are so blessed
we have water the animals the bugs the
birds
and the moon this perfect like we
couldn't exist without all of those
things no
like take away all the mosquitoes well
eventually the you know the trickle down
of the birds dying off or whatever it
would be
it's all connected one yeah it's like
the bees die we die
like that it's straight up facts and
it's just crazy to me how
people don't it's just that's what
people are not they're missing
is really they're missing the connection
to
the earth which we live on and reside on
and i believe that in my heart if you
feel disconnected and if you feel
depressed
please go to the forest for just
10 minutes even no phone
even no humans and just be
like how often do you allow yourself to
not be seen you know we're talking about
that being seen sometimes is
uncomfortable well a lot of us can't be
ourselves
because we're seen all the time what if
you can unsee
yourself and just allow the forest to
show you how beautiful you are
i think that's very important because we
you know we will use the example that we
used earlier so think about
listener if you go to you know you're
going back to your families for
a holiday it's christmas and um
it's you know all they see is the 15 15
year old version of you
and then anytime that you're not
matching up with who they knew you to be
as a little girl or a little boy the
people around you like
make jokes or they try to you know they
buy you the same thing that you loved
when you were 14.
i'm just a way different person blah
blah but i think that
if you really you know me as like a uh
in you as well as a just a chameleon
personality like able to kind of like
mold and like
be what what needs to come up in this
situation to make it the most
comfortable for everyone
um a lot of times we get lost in that
like a lot of times we get
when we're constantly surrounded by
people or even our phones which now
connect us to
an image of what we think we are
especially with social media
we aren't ever really able to shut down
like okay when nobody is around when i'm
not being what everybody else
needs or what i think is going to jive
the most with everybody
when i'm not arguing saying yes or no in
my head
with i am that 15 year old person or i'm
not
there really is something pretty
profound that starts to happen you start
really questioning like wait what
what do i care about what do i what do i
want to think about what is what do i
want out of this life while i'm here
like all these things i think that
getting out
especially in nature take your shoes off
yell as loud as you can
like just go out there like just give
yourself an hour give yourself something
just set
i'm going to go out here and i'm going
to do this and i'm not expecting
anything
i'm just going to see how it feels and
you know
i think we're so connected to technology
and our busy busy world that
just that alone would be pretty profound
for a lot of people
and it's so crazy to me um i'm not
putting anyone down but
i just cannot not be
touching plants every day and i realize
oh that's one of my gifts
you know because to me it's like why
doesn't everyone have a garden my baby's
like
you have a green thumb like anything you
touch grows he's like not everyone has
that ability and to honor that
and um but to me it's like i feel like
one of my reasons i am here is to
reconnect people with the planet and to
appreciate
plants more and to appreciate our food
more and to think about
where your food's coming from and um
something that i really try to embody
too is i like to just eat
one ingredient foods and put them
together
simple right our body is really simple
um i've been trying to not eat anything
in packages
trying to even bottles like um of course
i still eat
top ramen and cheetos sometimes
unfortunately i have my vices but
i've been really conscience of i've been
trying to just do like even liquids
like just allowing my body to not be so
focused on digesting food all day right
and to just
feel what it feels like to be an
energetic being when you always have
food in your body your body's working
it's digesting right it's like
do you do fasting at all have you yeah
when you i listen to you talking like oh
i intuitively did that but i just never
called it that
you know but i intuitively don't eat in
the morning i mean i
i'll drink this 16 ounce smoothie for
like four hours in the morning like
i made this at 10 i'll probably drinking
it until like two
and it's not that i don't know what i i
even smoke
and i just i don't i don't crave
things like i used to well a lot of
something that i that i noticed too i
mean because i still have my vices i
still have times where i'm like i'm
going to
kill this bag of chips like i have i
have like binge eating problems that i'm
still working with me too
but like there is the way that i started
thinking about it and the way that
started making sense and then i was like
listening to uh
i think dr mark hyman i think
but but he talks he's a great person to
listen to about like what the food does
to us and
our gut is vastly connected with our
brain yeah it's it's i mean a lot of our
serotonin you know what's it 90
i know we're always on the cusp of the
same thing um you know the way that i
see it
so when i had i had stopped a few years
back i had stopped drinking i was like
dude it hasn't been
i don't remember the last time maybe it
was since i was 14 when i first had a
drink that was the last time i went a
month without drinking
like just not drinking every day but
it's just the regular life is we drink
friday it's friday we're going to drink
it's thursday not
we're maybe going to drink saturday for
sure just this weird continuous thing
but i think that
continually having our same habits and
not giving ourselves like 30 days or 60
days
i think that like those materials like
if you say
let's say like a a certain sugar
um makes us it pops thoughts into our
head
if you keep feeding it so like if you
have the same alcohol every day
if you have the same alcohol once a week
you're feeding that false voice
yeah right yeah it's it's like it's
almost like
having a little mini curse of like our
thoughts always
cue it in and our thoughts always like
oh this is why i want that
and here's why i want that and oh yeah
it is fun because you're going to go
hang out with your friends and that's
good and blah blah but really like that
could the root of that could just be
because you have like an addictive
chemical in your stomach
that is making you continually want want
to get it like the same way
also called the parasite parasite
yeah that's a good word for it so in the
four agreements um
i don't know if you read that but it
talks about
that humans all have a parasite
in the parasite almost like ego and you
feed it what it wants
you feed it the the partying you feed it
the education
you feed it the certain food the certain
alcohol the certain experiences you feed
this thing
a certain thing okay i don't know but
like it's called the parasite basically
so yeah with like
your body wanting certain things um your
body wants to actually heal it's just
some things in your body are creating
chemical
reactions chemical responses creating
false thoughts
because i have i'll have like 16
sometimes different opinions in my head
and i'm like having to like filter out
like
and what is it and then when i literally
if you go
what does my higher self want and then
it's like computing
and then you get your answer you know
what i mean because no i don't think my
body does probably want
top ramen you know what i mean it's like
i was just talking to you about that i'm
like oh i'm probably low on salt
but this is just what i see right now so
this is how i think i need to eat or
and i i struggle with being binge eating
too i just never like really
started looking at it until recently
because i will eat a whole bag
i don't just eat a half or like a
handful like i'll eat concentrate you'll
pass that halfway point of like
i might as well finish yeah yeah i'm
already halfway i might as well just eat
the whole bag
i'm not just gonna leave this much left
in the bag literally
but it's like a lot but then that's like
allowing you to finish it and justifying
it
and then my boyfriend's in bed he's like
can i have some chips and i'm like
more chips seriously like ate them all
like and i'm not even consciously aware
of it
and thankfully lately i've just been
like i don't need to eat
all of that what made me think i need to
eat the whole thing
you know and i've been realizing that i
don't need a lot of food
to be you know i'm not and maybe if i'm
working out but i'm
i'm really not i don't need that much
anymore yeah i i think that we
our food is so non-foodie that it really
doesn't cleanse what it needs to cleanse
it's just the best that we have like i
i was just talking with shaylee about it
we were at um anode tap house
and they have like some older photos
from like the 40s or 60s or something
of the building the antidote to house
like what it was before
and they had um there was like this cool
old car parked and there was like all
these
older gentlemen you know and they're all
dressed all nice and i was just noticing
and i noticed it a lot
but i notice how how their faces like
there's more you know they're thinner
for sure like that's just an inevitable
like americans have are just bigger now
and whatever's from so many ways but
like just the kind of like the chubby
swelling in their faces wasn't there
that like everybody has now
that inflammation yeah we're our
constant inflammation yeah
you know i'm not a fan of inflammation
uh it's it's interesting to think of
like
if you put something in your body that
you don't know
what 20 of the 23 ingredients are
tell me why you think that's good for
you
straight up do you read ingredients on
your food also
fun fact the us fda doesn't require
food companies to label everything that
goes into the food
they're also allowed to change words of
sugar into alternative words so you
don't know what sugar
they'll break it down it'll be three
different ingredients they're like what
are those and then you look them up and
you realize it's just sugar they just
broke down three different parts of
sugar
i think there's like 22 different
alternative names for
sugar um oh sugar-free sugar-free calls
alzheimer's
so really realistically you're craving
sugar i tell you what
a mango some strawberries
blueberries raspberries you won't have
it
you know we just don't want to eat
healthy sometimes because it's too much
it's too hard to cut that it's too much
what's too much for your health right
well so let's think joe rogan talks
mouth pleasure he says that
i love when he talked about that because
i'm like dude yeah
it simplifies it and you're like okay
that is what it is and you start
you have those little battles where
you're about to take another bite and
you're like is this just mouth pleasure
is this just
but i i think that the way that so like
even the fda we if it's
okay it's safe for humans i'm pretty
sure that the fda you just have to test
it for six months and in six months as
long as it didn't kill him or have any
adverse side effects then you're good
release it to the public
it's like medicine too yeah it's it's
oh my gosh and i think that
it's just the the way that we we're
poisoned yeah we really are
we're poisoned and we go to the doctor
and we get more poison
it's an endless cycle of poison because
you're controlled
your minds are literally controlled with
your
food with your water um they don't want
you to feel good
if you feel good you're not in their
control you don't need them
you don't need their food you don't need
their medicine you don't need their
knowledge you don't need them
and when you're at that point they don't
you're you're the
you know my whole life i thought this
way was crazy they're the crazy ones
they're not eating meat or cheese and
they're being naked in the forest with
candles they're crazy no they're alive
yeah
it's crazy how we like i thought about
that when i did i tell you about the uh
my experience with the naked bike ride i
didn't do it
i saw it um and it literally like in
that moment i hadn't really thought much
about it like
i didn't think yes or no about it but my
me and my friend jessica a while back
ago
we saw it and it went past this we're in
portland we end up just we stood there
for 20 minutes 15 minutes at least
and just were watching it and like oh my
god it's crazy to think that
we think these people are the craziest
mofos ever
well clothes like where we
do our do monkeys wear clothes like do
any other species wear clothes you know
it's because we
they made the women and so sexualized
right
they just over sexualized us and then
they make us feel bad for
being sexual it's like am i being sexual
because i'm wearing this
or are you just like prone to think that
because of how society's taught you
yeah it shouldn't women you shouldn't
feel bad to
dress how you want to dress because we
are goddesses we
literally souls come out of our vagina
yeah that's crazy
like we are portals like we are women no
friends jake but women
are powerful you shouldn't feel like
you can't wear this you can't wear that
because you'll get sexualized you know
what it's like
we literally we are the power like i
literally was talking my friend like
souls
come through us and enter our bodies
right we are
poor we are a living portal right but
men
in the government they know that and
they try to like suppress the
women and they try to like
that's the problem a lot of it is a
masculine feminine war
within ourselves within the planet like
there's no balance everyone could use
some more feminine energy in my opinion
and
powerful feminine energy not like the
nurturing like no like the powerful
right feminine energy of like yeah we do
bring life onto the
planet like we do matter i feel like
women have been suppressed
so long look at that women can't even
half the woman on the planet can't even
show their bodies
they get stoned to death they only show
their eyes women's clits are getting cut
off in some countries
yeah like women if you don't know these
things like if you're a woman in america
be proud it's the fact that you
can just be
the fact that you can talk the fact that
you can drive i think about that all the
time
oh folk america no no no no no no we
have so much freedom
i mean our government sucks but we're
safe to be a
female right if you compare it to a lot
of places like oh your ankle showed
you're getting thrown in the chokey
you're down before really like really
how it is when dane went to jerusalem he
was talking about how like
if he waved at a woman and a man saw
a man wave at her that she would never
be allowed to get married
oh my gosh that's crazy doesn't know
he's like trying to just like
talk you know he's just ruining
marriages left and right
they're like in the middle of like the
river though they're like on a kayak and
these girls are on a kayak and like
the guys like oh we can't you can't talk
to them like they won't
no one will marry them because another
man looked saw them well so imagine how
how we act different like as we go about
our lives and we see people make it we
make economically away we do whatever
imagine like how different their entire
24-hour day is that's what i'm saying
like
no one they don't look up so depression
for example like
think about someone with depression is
their their shoulders are forward and
maybe their heads a little down
their posture isn't lifted their chest
isn't super exposed their throat is
their throat and their neck isn't
isn't out yeah they're crunched in and
so imagine not
imagine walking around for fear of
accidentally making eye contact with a
man
and to feel that that we feel that too
because we're all connected
well that's why for me like it's so
important for me to share my voice
it's one of my gifts channeling is a
gift
those of you who can talk and want to
talk or those who need to write need to
write
i read this thing it's like what how
many books
are not getting published because of our
fear of being hurt or
being seen but like you we need to share
and express
our thoughts because they can change
people's lives
and to talk for those who can't straight
up and to spread awareness for the
issues that are going on not just the
ones that we see in our immediate little
zip code area like look outside the box
like there's so much going on
like yeah the virus thing but dude like
straight up there's people like villages
getting cut down
and slaughtered and like not to be
negative but just to really realize that
some people have it
so much right like fearful and like
to to realize that our lives maybe
aren't that bad
yes yeah i agree i mean it
there's so many crazy things going on
like there's you know at any point
especially now like the last you know
year like during this pandemic
everything's like worse like
australia burned up all these animals
gone like there's
there's countries where we're on the
edge of having
12 million of them without food next
year like these sort of things are
all over and when we you know we want
our specific things and over here oh my
gosh she made my coffee wrong
oh my god what right i get like that
though
i'm like you know it's like wow they
made a mistake like let's just be nice
and tell them
but it's like and then you're putting
negative energy on someone who's just
like trying to be
getting paid minimum wage and just like
trying to do their job you know what i
mean well
and we leave even on their end there's
such a disconnect with like people don't
like to be told that they're wrong
people don't like to be told no people
are used to people being mean
so it's like oh this person didn't like
my drink like i gotta protect myself i'm
going to put up my my boundaries or i'm
going to put up my
my i guess not good boundaries
barriers rather and people come at each
other with contempt
on accident too in that same way i think
it's interesting
how quickly people allow other people's
reactions to control
their current reality um that's a huge
one that i've been working on i feel
like
i think it's like like
so someone says something to you and
their intent might have not been to make
you upset but now you're upset
instead of allowing yourself to react
allow yourself to respond
and to think why is this making me upset
[Music]
why does this make me want to react
instead of not respond obviously this
takes time
i'm still working on this lesson but
something i'm realizing is
i think about buddhists and i think
about monks and they're not screaming at
each other
you know what i mean like they don't you
could tell them their mom died and they
would probably
like understand that mm-hmm you know
what i mean this is the way
this is the one i'm experiencing
tranquility
and um i think we react sometimes
because it's expected
for us to react or sometimes like that's
just what we've always done and it's a
defense mechanism
to react if i react this way maybe
they'll stop
yeah i'm just trying to protect myself
like i don't i won't get yelled
at if i yell louder first it's a weird
thing
but it's like why can't we just both
like chill down and just communicate
and feel like we're both being heard
because i don't know about you but when
i'm yelling at someone they probably
aren't hearing me i don't even hear
myself when i'm yelling
it's like rage yeah nobody's listening
when you're yelling no
no one's listening to you it's actually
doing the opposite effect
and you wonder why nothing's changing in
your relationships it's because you're
not changing how you're reacting or
responding
yeah i mean i i think a huge thing is a
i had recommended in one of the podcast
um intro but anthony demaio has a book
called awareness
and it's a lot of stuff that like any of
the spiritual teachings anything that
like
um i feel like that you or i would
stumble upon it
it's it really is this thing that's like
awareness is such an important tool it's
like the first thing
it's like just to see like awareness am
i getting mad
oh am i being overly emotional am i um
and not feeling shame about it because
when you feel shame about it you like
buckle down on it
you you're like you fix it of course
here's why and you find an answer but i
feel like if you're like
i know that honestly i don't really want
to
mostly really never want to be mad like
right i want to i want to be logical and
i want to like not have my emotions
catapult me and
and put me in a chokehold so i think
that when you have the awareness
um that that's that's a good book
awareness by anthony demaio if anybody
wants to check that out
but um it just kind of shows you like
all these little moments where we're
just on our 95
subconscious autopilot you know we're
just doing the same thing part of like
doing something you don't want to do
though
i think it's part of it i was just
talking about waking up for a job you
don't like
packing your lunch for a job you don't
like going to a job you don't like
spending your time 10 hours a day
somewhere you don't like you
think you come home you're gonna want to
like
you know what i mean yeah when you're
getting a lot of your time away
to something you don't care about the
time when you're not there
is probably not gonna that's my reality
anyway when i was working
you know for say as a nurse i kept
trying kept trying and
man it's just not for me right now it's
i haven't found the right path i haven't
found
um it's just not something that i
thoroughly enjoy
you know i thought i wanted to help
people and i do but not in that way
i kept forcing it because everyone you
know you went to school you know you did
it you're a nurse it's a cool thing so
many people want to be a nurse
i'm like that's great that's their
experience that's not your life i'm like
but the thing is it doesn't really make
me happy
it makes me stress i have anxiety i have
ptsd from so many experiences of babies
almost dying on me and it just gives me
anxiety
i don't want to be that person to
be in control of someone's breath like i
don't want to be the person to have to
like that's just not me i don't want to
be in trauma anymore and i think when i
went into nursing
i liked trauma because that's how i was
raised i grew up in a chaotic household
i grew up with screaming i grew up with
not talking i grew up with figuring it
out on my own and i grew up with
just all my own kind of resources and i
feel like
as a nurse you're kind of doing the same
thing you're having to trust your
instincts and my instincts are really
good you're having to react i'm
really good at reacting nursing
is reacting really fast like
it's crazy to me how people want to go
into trauma
you know what i mean it's like what kind
of person is that that they want to
experience
other people's trauma every day that was
me i thought i wanted to be an er nurse
trauma i love it really you want to be
around people's trauma like and that's
great if you do
nurses thank you doctors thank you like
we need you
but i'm like what really wanted that
that was like a traumatic i was like my
childhood trying to come out and heal
like i was comfortable in trauma i liked
it i like being the person for people to
come to
yeah yeah and it but it was like trying
to heal my own trauma and then once i
like was in nursing school and i was
like
this is too much energy for me i'm so
sensitive
i can't be around this i can't be in a
hospital
i couldn't be even in a i couldn't even
have one client
i got to i couldn't take on that energy
because i just am not
good yet at protecting my energy for 12
hours
and for me a nurse and who i really am
are two different people
so i was constantly battling myself
and when you're battling yourself trust
me it sucks
you don't know who the you are yeah
i mean it's i think a lot of people go
through that
yeah i worked i worked at warehouses for
five years and it was like
i would almost get that same thing that
you were talking about people like oh
like how how did you get that job
or like how like it was like i was so
lucky to have this job they're like oh
like i
applied for that i never got an
interview i could be like stuff like
that it's like
what do you mean like it's like almost
like
there's places where there's a lot of
people sometimes should be telling you
that you're
grateful but if you're not feeling
grateful for it maybe that's something
you should look at you know
maybe that's like oh like maybe like
maybe this isn't for me like it was it
was great for me for those five years
because i can
i was was it financially great for you
though it was yeah
that's the thing that's the thing is
that the only reason why you're doing
something
it was a lot of safety right yeah was
that growth
was that comfortable i was able to like
do my djing on the weekends and then
towards the end i was able to like go to
school in between
but then it just got too much like when
i'm really like
do you think that caused a lot of
depression oh doing something you don't
want to do
one of the most primary causes of my
depression so
cutting that out allows you to heal yeah
that's how i feel with nursing then i
started healing right like when i quit
where i was like
stuff got way darker for a couple months
and then you know healing starts coming
out
but that's the thing like so many of us
do things we don't want to do because
it's
comfortable you know it's okay to be
broke
and work on yourself yeah truly is
it's okay to not have that money's not
the only currency no because when you
work on yourself and you become in
direct alignment with what you're
supposed to be doing on the planet the
universe just supports the
frick out of you people start coming to
you for business ideas people the
opportunities start arising you start to
get those million dollar ideas in your
head
because you're opening space yeah and
you start acting on it and you start
writing more and you start doing more
and you start realizing and seeing the
worth in your creativity that's
something that i never saw in myself
until this last year but i'm a creative
being and i love to create
like i never had space or put time on
that that was never a value in my life
do you do you find that we've talked
about social media and how how it comes
to that too i feel like
you're so on your game when it comes to
social media you've completely like you
don't care what anybody thinks
you're completely yourself on social
media do you want me yeah okay
i'm like well yeah really you feel that
way see i don't even believe it
oh yeah no no i totally do because we've
discussed this before
um i i so i even had like like back in
the day i would do
i i was constantly had dj mixes that i
would upload like i love them on
soundcloud
yeah i missed that i had a few accounts
get deleted from copyright stuff just
because when you're mixing other
people's music like
yeah but um i i would literally back
then
people would like comment that i don't
know or even somebody that i'd met
before or something
or it'd be something as soft as like
this transition needs work
or like they would comment or like say
something about my work
and i would take it as just this
horrible like i would think about it all
the time
i would like question if i should be
djing like it's so
crazy so you just answered one of your
questions
but what was it what like what's kind of
holding you back from that stuff
like when you are producing and stuff
like allowing other people's
yeah it well it's other people's
opinions but i also i have like
feelings of so like i'll feel confident
and and then somebody will comment
something like that
and then it won't be just particularly
them but it'll be like wait let's be
real though like do i am i that good
am i do people really care what it like
it makes it it starts this whole like
stupid silly
like self-worth saying thing really
and it's uh it's just it just gets so
tied up with
opinions what other people care about
you but also you are good though
thank you thank you jay we people also
think that we're going everybody's
trying to figure each other out in weird
ways like
i didn't say that that transition was
good i'm just showing you my art here's
what i did
you know we're always trying to people
are always trying to negate i think
and when it comes to social media it's
like oh you don't line up with this
thing that i think that you're trying to
be
so i'm going to comment on that and i
think that
social media can kind of keep us locked
in that in some senses but being able to
like when you post like it doesn't
matter what anybody says
i haven't honestly had anyone be rude to
me yeah see
hey realistic though nobody was really
ever mean to me like i was just super
sensitive i'm still sensitive but
i would just like one seriously one
comment would be your transition needs
work which is
if that was another dj commenting and
like he's giving me advice
he's trying to help you yeah but like
when you're sensitive and you're
um you've taken it so personal
at least i would too i no i did i would
do the same thing
um someone one time was like oh your
dancing is weird i'm like i deleted it
and i was like that's so silly i don't
care oh my gosh
who i don't even know these people why
did i allow
yeah you're weird like if you were a
bunch of people just like you
if they were dancing they'd be like dude
this is the most normal dancing i've
ever seen
they're like i love your dancing i do
the same thing every morning and it's
just crazy because
um i have stru i go back and forth with
like being in my body
like um i love to dance
that's something that i've always
enjoyed um i've never really been like
ashamed of that
um but when it comes to like being sober
dancing
not that i can't do it because i do it
every morning but it's like
oh she's sober and because everyone used
to think i was like always rolling or
what is she on and i would like nothing
you know i just allowed like the energy
to move through my body and then i think
sometimes it's triggering for people oh
i think so like be
not only am i in my light spiritually
mentally emotionally but then to show it
physically
it really causes people to be
uncomfortable because wow like they
can't move i can't move my body like
that yes everyone can
it's just so primal for me i'm so
connected to my roots
i feel indian at my heart i am indian um
to me it makes sense to be dancing
around a fire with my friends
that just seems like we everyone should
be doing drum circles every month that's
something that i want to start doing
because
we should be dancing with our friends
and like getting it out
and like being able to feel like you can
spiritually express yourself physically
has been changing like
like wow i want everyone to feel like
this it just feels good like it's a
great way to start your day to just
physically express yourself spiritually
though yes
yes i agree like i say i like to get out
of the way
make sure i'm not like trying to to be a
certain thing i like to just get out of
the way
and you dance and your body tells you
what you what you're doing what you're
going through your body tells you where
to move and how to move
and then afterwards there's this light
feeling of like of course you just moved
everything around your body that's great
in a million ways but there's also this
like oh yeah i was taking myself too
serious like
big deal yeah yeah and like to realize
that like animals move
like they shake and they do like weird
things they like stretch when they wake
up and like
every time we're animals you know and um
i think we've just forgot that we are
like
physical beings sometimes we get so like
structured
and we forget like how we can move you
know when we were younger no one care
but now it's like oh we're an adult
we're not allowed to like
you know and there's not a lot of space
for people to move like that you know
now we're at the bar and we act cool and
we sit at this bar table and anyone that
tries to dance is weird
it's like you remember house parties
like do you remember like what we used
to do
in like freaking grass and like
backyards in the woods
but like that's weird you know it's like
that's not there anymore it's like
why why do we shift out of that so i
sometimes get a little confused when i
see like the social media apps like tick
tock for example like
i like that it's getting getting people
dancing but i
sometimes so like a lot of times people
come come to the bar and i'm playing
and they'll request like a song that
they know all the all the moves to
and i think there's a big disconnect
there of like really dancing just like
moving your body and feeling how you
feel
and i want to perform this dance that
i've gotten good at it's like this very
robotic
version of dancing that's not dancing
because then it's like oh everyone knows
this dance it's normal
i'm moving be normal because this is
what the dance looks like so we're
normal
and in the dance floor will be packed
like literally like you play cupid
shuffle or something and that's
that's the one that's community yeah
yeah even though i'm like i don't know
for me like i like to just move my body
naturally but it's because people don't
know how to move their body so it's like
when something comes on that they do
know how to do it's like oh wow everyone
knows this song this is how we know how
to move it's normal
right you know what i mean it's like
those songs like um
like soldier boy in like seventh eighth
grade like everyone would dance because
everyone knew the moves
so it's like oh it's normal to move it's
okay to be seen right now because
everyone this is a normal thing but when
you're moving unstructured
and you're moving freely it does stress
people out
how can she move like that like i
remember people like staring at me and
like question like
is she on drugs yeah i mean sometimes i
was but i mean i wasn't always
you know what i mean i wasn't always on
molly at every party
like yeah so i actually had i used to
have this lady i totally forget her name
and i really wish that i had remembered
her name i introduced myself once she
was totally sweet um but she used to
come like
when i was playing around town she'd
come to like the bars that i'd play at
she would go to the club that i was
playing at
um and she would be there at 10 p.m like
right when i start
and she would be sober she'd drink
either like a soda or water she would be
by herself no friends like she would
come out she'd have one little table
she'd put her drink there in her purse
there and then she would come out and
she just she just dances
and she just she you know she doesn't
look around she doesn't care anybody
else doing she's just
closing her eyes a lot of times i
remember like i would hang out with
people
who i should have been more protective
of her now that i think of it
in a sense but i would hang out with
people who would say that exact same
thing like oh she's a meth head
she's a or she used to be a meth head so
she just she's out here being a weirdo
like
just absolute judgment on this woman for
being the only one on the dance floor
when realistically it's this triggering
thing in all of us that we wish we were
that one person on the dance floor first
i always try to be the first i don't
give a if the music is vibrating
high
because at least for me like when you're
playing it is very like spiritual
like you're putting your heart and soul
into it and like i do know you so it's
like obviously more fun to support you
but like
music is meant to dance to
like straight up like music is meant to
create
and when i was actually touching your
hands like melody notes were like
flowing out of them
so it's just crazy because you're like
supposed to
produce music and it's crazy to me that
you're not
doing more because you're supposed to be
doing that you've been doing that your
whole life intuitively you don't taught
you
the gifts that were taught you might
have been you ever hear a song and be
like maybe you wrote that like that
person's dead and like you don't you
know what i mean like you've probably
been making music your whole life
your whole existence yeah and you have
no idea like there's a reason that you
are naturally good at it and there's a
reason you don't think you're good at it
because you really are good at it
that's so complicated i get that though
it is funny because i
then you're always trying to improve it
yeah i'm always trying to
you know it's it's so silly i
all sometimes i'll compare myself like
i'll hang out with people who are like
really good at
being musicians really good you can't
think they're really good unless you're
really good
you can't see a trait in someone else
that you don't embody or you wouldn't be
able to identify that trait
the people you look up to you have the
ability to be
that because think about who you look up
to
i don't know the people you know i don't
think you know what i mean i can
appreciate it but you actually oh
they're really good
at this you know that because you have
the ability to embody
what they're really good at right does
that make sense
yeah i mean it does i understand what
you're saying
i i i think but you don't believe in
yourself so then you can't
you don't see it like that yeah but
that's your own blog a lot of the times
yeah i know and it's something i'm
always working on um a lot of the times
it's it's this sense of like
i do have something now where like when
i play piano for a few hours like when i
when i practice these stop right there
who plays the pianos for a few hours
right an artist yeah i mean listen to
yourself
how many of you here play the piano for
a few hours for fun
and you teach yourself and this is how
you're spending your adult life right
that's an artist you're dedicating time
to art
like the more you embody that if the ego
doesn't like to hear the word artist
don't say it but that's really what
you're doing i play the piano for a few
hours like so casually like i wish i
would make myself play the piano for a
few hours
it's so annoying because there's this
perfectionism of like i'm not good
enough which is what you need like it's
this
fuel that's like is carried on a stick
that keeps me going keeps me improving
and keeps me like learning and trying to
trying to push the edge of what i know
but
uh it's it's
it's funny you know it's it's i i don't
know why why i
tangle myself up so often because i have
i have musician friends who i hang out
with who i look up to who i think are so
much better than me in every single way
but like they'll they'll be like dude
you're a piano player like what are you
they'll say the same thing but it's this
thing that i constantly have trouble
facing i wonder how many people have
something just like that you know like
artists creators i wonder how many
people
like listening have something they don't
give themselves and like not
just yes that but like how many artists
did we not even think was art until they
died van gogh
picasso the some of the greatest artists
musicians
that we have scientists theories aren't
proven till now they thought they were
when the world wasn't flat and the guy
thought it was around oh he's
crazy hundreds years later he's right
yeah just because your vibe isn't
what's energetically around you doesn't
mean that it's not
art you know what i mean like i create
stuff i do things and i don't think it's
worth anything or i don't think it's
anything into it people like oh that's
so good
it's like why do we need the validation
of others to think what we do is that
like good
what is what is art to you jay like what
is it
i think everything yeah everything
god everything that i don't like that
word
creator is art
and talking is art your clothes are art
what you choose to eat is art but that's
just how i live my life
i try to i try to embody art because art
is beautiful art is love
um i cut flowers art
you know what i mean i'm feeding my cats
that's art like i'm taking
i think being present is art being
creative in how you choose to do things
is art i think when you're disconnected
it's not but i think when you're
in alignment with yourself it is art
like i make my smoothies and i put
little mint sprigs in it and i'm putting
different ingredients in it and i'm
being present and i think to me that's
art i'm cooking
it's art for me i'm watering my plan so
just the right amount like
i think just being a creator yeah that's
why i was just thinking about creation
creating like i think the word art is in
create
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
so i think just like being a creator
which we all are is being art and if you
just
and body that more you're always being
an artist because you're always creating
because you're shifting through your
timeline and your energetic body
i think when you're doing stuff you
don't want to do i don't think that's
art
i think when you hate your life and you
don't when you you go to a job you don't
like i don't think that's art
to me for me my personal experience it
wasn't art for me and that's why i
didn't enjoy it and i think like
when i'm at the nursery and i'm doing
flower arrangements and i'm
redesigning like landscapes that's art
to me i'm creating people's experience
i enjoy it if you work at like
burgerville and you love making
burgers that's art and you can feel that
you know it doesn't matter what you're
doing if you work at a car wash and you
thoroughly like making people's cars
clean
that's art we all have it it's just what
you
if you like doing it i think is when it
is something you're creating
yeah we don't i feel like when it comes
to art we don't often give ourselves the
individualism that comes with it a lot
of times we're like well it's not art to
these other people so it's not really
who's the people yeah who's that you
know some people like splatter one paint
on the wall and like sell for three
million dollars because
that person made it that's art i can
feel the emotion
but you know what i mean everyone's are
so subject there's so many artists
some aren't you buy with some art you
don't and what we are attracted to as
individuals is going to be different to
our neighbor
there's some people's things they have
in their house that i would never have
in my house but that doesn't mean that
it's not
art it's just not the art that i want in
my space
yeah and everybody has their own like
everybody has like
only you can do exactly what you can do
yeah everybody has their own individual
like i always tell myself when i'm like
listening to someone else and then i get
inspired to create
i always tell myself because i'm like oh
i don't want to make like that they've
already done or something i tell myself
you couldn't copy them if you tried
no like we can we can all only
create our own art from us like it's
there's nobody can create the same thing
that you can create
100 and because you're in that time and
space
you not them you might have been
inspired by the frequency that they
admitted and you might have leveled up
and you might have joined their
frequency so you could produce something
on the same frequency
but it's not going to be the same item
but it's going to be admitting the same
frequency maybe
if that makes sense it could be similar
to them because it's the same energetic
vibration
but that artist isn't going to hear your
song like oh this is the same as me he's
like oh wow this feels good this sounds
like kind of something that i could like
that i make too but it's not gonna be
like oh he copied me
you know what i mean like and it's crazy
i'll listen to other people who channel
they said the same thing i did but it's
just because we're in the same frequency
and these aren't my words if you
identify
yeah if you identify yourself with what
you say i don't
yeah i'm just a channel dude you don't
know even right now like you don't know
what you're gonna say i don't know what
i'm gonna say next
i don't plan it it's just flowing when
you're an open channel to it especially
after reiki your
all your channels are opened you're
allowing universal energy to just flow
through you out your vessel
yeah it's i just embody
i'm like a living walking channel so
have you experienced
um musician channels like have you have
you so so for example i listen to this
guy um
uh uh douglas murray maybe is his name
murray um uh
i really want to think of his name but
he's he was this piano player i'll
i'll pop it in um he's this piano player
i was down in
um san diego somewhere down there
and we essentially this cool story where
we stumbled upon on a beach this guy
playing a grand piano and there was
people with
bluetooth headphones around him it was a
silent disco and it was like
oh oh are you are you guys here for the
silent disco like wait what is this and
she explained it to us
and she's like it's about to start right
now and we're like
okay and me and my co-workers like we
put on headphones sit down and this dude
he explains what he's doing yeah he
expresses i don't know if he calls
himself
i don't know if he uses the word
channeler but he may but he essentially
like
he does healing through through sound
and he so he just had grand piano on the
beach
he had a door that you could do for like
an art installation take a photo or just
experience it
that was in the sand and when you open
the door you'd be like facing the ocean
so you can do that as your experience
but put on headphones there's like i
don't know 50 60 people
throughout the beach um and he just he's
creating the same and we were talking
about that right he probably created the
same
frequency for everyone to experience
which was high vibration
and it connected you through sound yeah
it did i mean he started playing he was
like i'm going to take you on this
journey i'm you we're going to go
through some emotions like and you just
when you give in to it you really it's
it's a lot of surrender
yeah yeah it's like we really just like
trying to have expectations you just
for me for me it makes sense for me to
tell myself
step out of the way and allow you know
and that's that's almost like a
i don't know it just makes sense for me
but anyway so so he
he he would play songs like it's not
like he plays like discord with discord
and you know that in jazz school
it means this exact thing no he's just
like creating this
this flow this channel this like direct
whatever like he's just playing with his
fingers you know
it's up and down it moves your emotions
as a listener
um it was incredible but it's a i feel
like it
i'm super obsessed with it um but have
you ever
have you ever experienced like a music
channel or like
anything um i'm sure you've met a couple
channels now
i have not i've been to like silent
raves
um but i have not been to like something
like that but
someone i really love is fkj and he does
stuff like that
where he played the piano and he had
multiple people with headphones just
sitting around him
yeah so um i listened to it on youtube
but i've not had one personally but that
is something that like i told you with
the sound bowls
is something that i do want to start
practicing with my own is having my
partner play the sound bowls and have
that personal
sound healing experience and that is
channeled and another thing
is when you're just being and you're not
thinking you're channeling
unless you're robot mode yeah but you
know what i mean like the flow state
like last night i literally grabbed a
piece of driftwood i'm like i want to
paint this blue
why does why i don't know i want to you
know what i mean like i don't know why i
want to paint it
and then i wanted to paint one red and
it literally looks just like the colors
over there and i'm like okay
cool like you know what i mean like so
it's just don't
when you want for me when i want to do
these weird random things i just don't
question i just do it yes it was a
release for me
yeah it felt good to just paint and it
doesn't it's not like i'm painting
a beautiful picasso picture when you're
not creating for anyone else just
but you're only creating just to create
it's a different kind of energy
i'm not going to sell this and make
money like i'm just creating because it
just feels good to allow
creative energies to flow through my
physical vessel
and to not think and to just paint
so does it so when you're when you're
channeling when you're just in that flow
state
does it feel like that too like
obviously initially there's this like
this urge towards i know i'm gonna do
this
and then so for me i say i kind of step
out of the way
and allow like the the peace or the
music or the whatever needs to to come
out come out like what
what's that like for you like yeah super
similar like for me a lot of it's music
like i do usually when i'm inspired it
is with just certain sounds or certain
vibrations and it starts by movement
and then it starts by like oh i should
record my experience because i feel like
this would allow
other people to be authentic and you
know when i'm recording myself for
instagram it's not for likes it's not
for the serotonin boost
it's not for the comments not for the
messages when i'm recording myself my
intention is to allow others
to give themselves two minutes to be
yourself you know every morning i'm just
dancing on my deck that's just something
i intuitively
do but to just show other people that
you can do that
you can do this like it feels great and
um
for me it's the first one on the dance
floor that's i always am
but just to for me creating i just want
other people to create you know i'm not
by any means like this prophetic artist
and i can just paint
and or i can just write or i can do all
these things i mean i bet if i
put my energy into it and that's
something that i wanted to do and i
really wanted to try i think anyone can
try to paint and learn and watch youtube
and i think we can try to do anything
but it's what is that really what i want
to do all the time for me it's just
what feels good how do i want to express
myself different ways to express myself
because i get bored
i can't just you know i get bored i have
adhd
how can i express myself today oh i'm
gonna cut this tree down and mesh it
with this tree and try to like cut
flowers and do
you know for me it's just working with
art with nature like for me it's
a lot of what i do is nature connecting
myself to nature
and seeing how nature's so beautiful and
bringing that into my space is something
that i thoroughly enjoy
i like that well because it it just
reminds me because like like for me with
the junkyard love thing it's just kind
of working with what i have
yeah you're right you're in a junkyard
and you got to make it work i love that
and it's cool that you do that with
nature it's like you just like you trust
the intuition of these things to tell
you what needs to go with this you know
i mean
i do that though like anywhere i go you
can ask any friends i make flower okay
i do nature everywhere i go willow
willow grove i've made the dopest thing
like i just
that's just what i do i feel so
connected to the earth even though i'm
not from it i just feel like
people if they just looked around them
is so beautiful and i feel like that's
one of my gifts though
is to gather women gather you know i
feel like i'm a very good gatherer i
feel like i've gathered my whole
existence and i'm just really good at
showing what i gather in a beautiful way
and to me like i never thought anything
of it until other people acknowledged it
i'm like oh okay yeah i guess that is
kind of cool
and i just always am cutting flowers i
cut flowers every day i just thought
everyone did
what do you think like back in other you
know other
variations of human existence and other
like uh
in other times think about a shaman you
know we've mentioned shaman a couple
times like think about how
how close you're living to how a shaman
would live like
really yeah i mean i that word is so
heavy for me but so enlightening because
i've had a lot of people
call me that or ask if that's what i was
and um i guess there's this blockage for
me where
i feel like to be a shaman you have to
be like chosen
you know because i feel like
traditionally speaking when you're in a
tribe
but then i'm like but we're not in
tribes anymore you know but i am the
healer of my family
i am the one that people go to when
they're passing i do help my family
members pass i am the one
people are sick they come to me so i am
the healer of my family
but i am the healer of my town i'm doing
energy work i'm the healer of my friends
you know what i mean i i am this healer
and again you
being an artist i don't think of myself
like that
i don't think of myself as a healer
you know what i mean i just feel like
this is just what i do
or this is something that i thoroughly
enjoy if you had to define if someone
else had to define it for you
sure that's maybe what it sounds like
but you're just doing it yeah
and it's not that i don't think it's
amazing i think it is amazing but
i don't see it as this thing you know to
me it's like
i heal with my hands this is what i do
it's not something to be praised for to
me it's not something to be
and i think a lot about biblical
speaking not that i'm like christian but
like jesus healed with his hands and he
didn't
think anything of it because it's just
it's just something i think when you're
it's not even a gift that anyone can do
it i just want to do it it's something
that i'm drawn to
you know anyone can go get reiki attuned
it's not like you have to be special
you know what i mean you anyone can go
learn from who i learned from and do it
and practice you know it's just
is that in alignment with you is that
what you enjoy doing
i enjoy healing energy i always have
so to me it's like why have i been
resisting it
and i think we resist the thing we're
supposed to be doing the most
because it's scary to step into your
power yeah it is
it's scary it's crazy to me people like
feel healed after i'm touching them like
i still i'm like what the
you felt what from what you know what i
mean because to me i'm just putting my
hands i'm not
i don't have power you know what i mean
like you know when you get a massage
like oh that felt physically good like
you're physically rubbing the muscles or
oh i wouldn't got acupuncture you're
physically putting needles in but when
you're getting reiki
i'm not pushing on you yeah i'm just
placing my hands
you touched my feet very lightly and
then my arms and i think that was pretty
much it
like like but did you like feel energy
at all or like did you like i mean
it looked like you did i can't like
describe your experience but yeah
definitely i am
i did i i'd have a couple times where um
like certain areas would feel like
they're like lifting up or i would
i would kind of lose count of my breath
and then have to like almost stop
breathing or
your breathing changed a lot in
different parts yeah
yeah i i was like seeing and that tells
me like
energy's moving through you yeah to me
it was i think because i was i was
you know i practiced a lot of vipassana
um meditation so
like i was trying to get in that like
meditative state
trying but basically defaulting to it
right yeah and i feel like oftentimes
i'd be concentrating on my breath
because that's the most consistent thing
you can feel you know like right at the
edge of your nose and
in your belly you can feel where your
breath is it reminds me to be present
but uh like there'd be times where i'm
concentrating on my breath
but it would throw me off because my
breath would suddenly change like
without me
you know um it's just interesting i
i mean and it was it's
it's so funny trying to describe with
words
you know it's it's certain it's it's a
something jay it's it's a
something like i don't like i i think so
so my thing
with the podcast is i want you know
i want people to try something i want to
i want people to experience like if
there's something within you that's like
maybe i'm gonna give it a try like
run at it run at it do it try it
and i i think that like you know
different people have different
upbringings different people have
different things that that um
make sense or don't make sense to them
do you have to argue about what's
true or not true or what's real to you
what's not real to somebody else
like i think that if you allow yourself
to get out of the way like i say
and just experience it like you you know
you'll probably be surprised and it'll
teach you things about yourself
you notice how much you're swallowing
yeah
like loud you were like this
rock was like clearing your throat
chakra for you
yeah you know what's funny is i feel
like when i was swallowing it was almost
my
without even trying to it's almost like
my like okay you're good
like almost like a like a okay
that's also a sign of ascension
swallowing frequently
you're like are you sure it's not just
because i smoke a lot of weed
she's getting out of school it could be
that it could be from that too but
i'm just joking something else i do
listeners just because you weren't here
is i also use crystals for your
experience so i allowed jake to choose
crystals prior to his experience he
chose crystals for his heart which your
heart
has a lot of heat coming from which
obviously you have a lot of love
um he also chose a stone for grounding
um
which i don't think you're as grounded
as you think which not a lot of us
aren't that's why your feet were
twitching so much because it was
uncomfortable for you to be grounded
yeah my legs and feet definitely felt
yeah i was twitching i mean you want to
run if you want to move if you want to
you don't want to be here you want to
you know those are all signs and
symptoms of
not wanting to be grounded which goes
back to your chakra so as i was giving
you reiki some things that came up would
just saying things like i deserve to be
here
and like listeners you can say these
things to yourself you can just listen
but so many of us
need to hear that i want to be here you
know what i mean
like i love to be grounded
telling everybody that like i am an
artist
people this is stuff that came up for
you i've just wrote down people enjoy my
creations
my art matters i am a good person
i allow my light to shine i want to be
here i love having a physical vessel
so listeners i'm a firm believer in what
you say
is true so um i am a little witchy
but think about spells as your words
spelling
what you say is a spell it's true so
what you're choosing to say is how your
reality is going to be
i'm a firm believer in that if you like
can't say you love yourself if you it
feels hard it's hard for you to do or
it's hard for you to say you're a good
person it just it's just work it just
shows you work is it like i write people
affirmations and it's hard for them to
say these things about themselves
because they don't believe
it how many of you believe you're a good
person
you know what i mean like that's
something to think about and what what
makes you think you aren't
because of one experience with another
person 10 years ago you're not a good
person
shame and guilt energy suckers yeah no
doubt
lowest frequency shame guilt fear
you know what i mean like there's a lot
of things that i've done that
yes aren't something to be proud of
but it allowed me to have experiences
where i don't have to have them again
yeah i don't have to go through that
again
you learn from that one yeah whoa i'm
like oh wow i can't believe i used to
behave like that wow i used to
react that way wow i used to allow
myself to get in these situations that
were not safe for me
wow i was too trusting wow i didn't i
ignored these red flags i got myself in
these situations i did this i did that
and to just forgive it don't hold it
so heavy yeah you know we we think we
need to like hold out our own
execution like we need to hold out our
own like
like i don't deserve to
ever feel better because of that thing
or i don't
we we feel like we're our own judge and
we have to remind ourselves about that
judgment every morning or something who
is a judge
yeah who are you even judging who are
you straight up this is like part of
being
having no ego which is dangerous don't
just go no ego
like i did it's scary i think it's part
shrooms i think it's part
meditation but like i just don't
identify with who i see in the mirror
i don't i'm such the observer that
i think that's why i don't care as much
about my physical appearance and i never
really have
um you know i don't really like i do
face masks and hair masks but that's
just to make sure i'm like
taking care of my body but as for like
physical appearance
and stuff it's truly who cares about
that like it's good to be healthy
and it's good to do this but it's like
to me
i would rather spend my time like
meditating in the morning
than like putting an hour of makeup on
or something putting my hair in and if
that makes you feel good that's okay but
women
ladies like who's making you really want
to do that right right
i mean think about that makes you feel
good like anybody would say like well of
course it makes me feel pretty like of
course
it's for other people we accept that
yeah look at that but it's also what
makes me feel good think about that like
why why don't you feel good without it
though
yeah i'm not dissing anyone because like
we are all on our own journeys and stuff
but to just think about like i think we
just
unconsciously do i can't leave the house
with no makeup yeah
who told you that my heart hurts for
people who
like for women that are like afraid to
answer the door when they don't have
makeup on like they're you know i have
like a couple friends like their their
grandmothers are like that they're just
that's good
grandma's the same way vayne yeah i mean
i mean not my girl
my grandma was vain and she couldn't
people
she couldn't be seen without me yeah but
don't do that to yourself
right dang it don't do that to yourself
you know it sucks
and it's like we are all human yeah
you can you really get another thing is
this like do you want everyone to be
attracted to you
like that's my thing like do i want
everyone to be attracted to me sexually
physically
no i don't really want that attempt not
that that's giving you that attention
but it's like
why do you feel like you need to look
good like look good all the time
you know first because for me i have met
all my part
most of like being myself has allowed me
to meet who i really want to be and when
i was wearing makeup
and i didn't want to i was definitely
attracting different people
not saying that it's from that but i
think i embodied like a different
personality because it's really not me
like when i got ready and i spent hours
and because when you're putting hours
into changing how you look
you're gonna kind of maybe change how
you really are if you think about it
you're changing three hours to transform
how you look you know instead of
it's just different energy for sure i
mean and we're
it's it's funny humans are so incredible
we really find ways of like so
if we're not if we don't have the
confidence we're going to find a way to
get some sort of confidence or
the confidence that we feel we need so
like you get a new outfit and you you
know you put on your makeup and
and all these things like i'm someone
who used to be very high maintenance
when it came to like getting
ready like so so i know this too well
it's almost like
like the confidence that you're given
because of those things
kind of reminds you like okay well where
were you before that like what
what is it what was going on that you
didn't have so much confidence because
you should be confident in yourself at
all times like it's not
confident in my ability to be hotter
than all the other dudes in the room
you know right like it's silly yeah i
think too
um for me it's just about being
comfortable
you know i like to just feel comfortable
in my
where i'm at and being physical and i
think too
um to just show up and be yourself
i think a lot of people just can't do
that yet so i think they do cover
and they do do this and they do do that
and um you know they act hard or
they are unapproachable or they're just
this and you know and those are the
people that probably want attention the
most sometimes because i mean i've been
there where i like didn't want attention
but i really did
you know and you do things and you're
like abso you subconsciously
want attention because i don't want
anyone's attention but really you do
you know and it's like screaming for
help yeah like you want to be seen
yeah you're like but you're like oh i
don't you're low-key trying to not be
seen but by doing that you're actually
like trying to be seen it's like this
crazy thing we do
yeah to get this attention and we could
be so blind to it you know like our
subconscious really will like play
tricks on us like we think we're doing
exactly what we should be doing we think
we're
we're we think we're handling it but a
lot of times like letting go of that
control
it feels so good to just maneuver around
and to not stress about what other
people think about me
um that's something i still struggle
with like
i just i don't like when people look at
me
but still to this day um i don't know
what it is
but like people maybe i do it too but i
don't think people stare at me
like it gives me extreme i don't know
what it is maybe being seen maybe that's
part of like being in your light
but even if we're at chuck's produce and
like someone's staring at me like i get
in like uncomfortable i don't know what
that is i don't know if it's like
do you think maybe you're feeling like
they're thinking about you or something
in a sense
yes and throwing that at you and i think
sometimes it's like oh how can she be so
comfortable with herself and that's
questions that people ask me that make
me triggered it's like
oh you're just so seven like you're just
so free like you're just so you say
whatever you want
and you know and sometimes it's like and
i think it comes off as like they're not
the way i
am and they're like projecting how angry
they are that they aren't the way i am
and it's like making me
question it i'm like oh my god is this
bad to be myself
not no but you know but you get in this
mindset where it's like i'm making
people uncomfortable and i don't
and i spent my whole life trying to make
everyone comfortable but then being
myself makes people uncomfortable so i'm
like chronically going through that
battle
it kind of reminds me of um like i
always point out
like so say an older lady or or someone
who's like not really dressed they're
wearing a business suit or something
someone who you wouldn't expect to do
this thing
and they compliment you on your blue
hair they go like oh i like your blue
hair
a lot of times i would see those
situations as like you don't actually
like it you're just
noticing you know maybe they're wishing
that they could have blue hair but their
life isn't like matched up with it or
they're just
they're trying to say i noticed that you
have blue hair and that's pretty crazy
and they don't know how no else like
they don't know how else to say it
yeah i wonder if it's something like
that like people are trying to
we're always trying to figure each other
i know and it's like why can't we just
talk about it
yeah like i said like sometimes i'm like
you know they people at work will like
comment on my clothes or something
and it's like well like i wish i could
dress like you
like why can't you you can you know what
i mean why can't
i have a friend who's like i used to
dress like you know how you dress all
the time like how do i dress
please tell me like what do you mean
yeah like okay so i didn't realize you
have this whole image of how i dress
that's what i'm saying it's just crazy
because um
we are just such compare we compare so
much
um it's so all times oh wait
everything the first thing you do what
do you do for a living what's your bank
account statement
let me compare that financially to
uplift my emotions towards you right
whatever remember i was i was talking
about earlier i was like you know if i
had like a
a phd in neuroscience and people would
take me more serious
like no no that's not what i mean though
maybe ph if you're trying to talk to phd
people all the time yeah you probably
might need that but
to a normal person if you're dedicating
an hour
of study or more a day you know you're
learning
you know you might not have like the the
homework assignments or whatever but
like i think
when you start to do this self-work you
become a teacher
when you learn to heal yourself it's uh
a lot of people take this journey on and
to honor that
not a lot of people want to look at
themselves and heal that's okay
thankful it hurts but the fact that we
can do it and we want to do it and we
want to help other people do it as a
gift
yeah i mean and it's it's this crazy
thing that
i again i need to expand my vocabulary
on that word but
it's this it's this thing that once you
start healing once you start like doing
the work once you start
i don't know leaning into it like it's
always anybody that you listen to or
like who has healed or like that
has like changed their lives
dramatically in these ways like they're
like
it's hard but it's so worth it like i
see so many things that i didn't realize
i didn't see
before it's just this it's such a
clarity like it's
it comes with its fog for sure yeah but
it's it's also this clarity and that the
clarity comes from
almost the sharpening of your intuition
in a way the more you heal and lean into
it the more you kind of have like your
inner intuition your inner voice that's
like
telling you or
less answers and just wanting more
action
yeah and then like when you stop
questioning yourself you
your intuition can guide you
it's like okay um i collect i like
do moon water my mom's like oh how's
your moon water going like it's so
normal in my life
you know the things that i think are
normal people around you will start
accepting it too if you think it's true
but if you're you know let's say you're
someone new into crystals and you get
crystals and someone is being rude to
you
crystally okay cool like don't share it
with them then
keep it to don't question yourself if
you're into something and you want to
learn more about it ask someone that's
into it
i guarantee you if you ask ini nam like
this if you ask me questions i always
answer i'm always down to teach
grant i'm not like i don't know
everything but i
do know that i've been working on myself
for 12 years now
i mean i'm 25. i've been doing the work
since i was at like 13
and obviously like my growth is
different than everyone but i've been
learned i've been consciously learning
about a lot of things that
you know we can teach each other i want
to teach i want to come on podcasts and
to teach and to just
if i can like shift anyone's mindset
into a higher frequency like that's what
i want to do
yeah 100 and i think like a lot of us
have things to teach we just don't even
like give ourselves credit for it
so many of our friends have stuff to
teach so they just like don't credit
like we all are into
our own things it's like we all have
something to teach each other but like
we don't give ourselves that time and
space to acknowledge that we are
have the ability to teach each other
well and i think one thing that as
individuals like listeners is everybody
in their life can do
is just be more encouraging like
something i try to do on here is like
like i'll take someone's dream that i
know about and i'll be like let's
amplify it on the podcast like tell me
about your dream you know
it's like i think that more people just
need a little bit of of belief like
we don't need it you know don't don't
wait for someone else to tell you that
you can do this thing but like
i think a lot of us can you know if
someone's telling you something weird
like it doesn't matter if you agree with
it it doesn't matter if it's exactly how
you think
if you if you love someone if you love
one of your one of your friends like
and they have this thing they're leaning
into that seems to like
make them happy or it seems like it's an
answer for them like doesn't have to be
an answer for you like i have a
my uh um my mom actually in her
childhood
well not childhood her best friend from
a long time ago
um she recently like my mom was kind of
like weirded out she got into i think it
was mormon um
just a religion in in this her friend
deals with with a lot of depression um
has dealt with a lot of things in this
new community that she got a part of um
just started to get her out of the house
she started really enjoying it like i
had doctor she was doing great she loved
it
and my mom was kind of having trouble
like i don't know what i think about
that and like i don't
think it's kind of crazy and you know
what whatever like she just hadn't
really super thought about it
um and then like after we talked it was
kind of like
think about how good this is for that
person like you take yourself out of the
situation your beliefs like
this person is now like laughing more in
there and they're more themselves and
they found a community that like
you know maybe you're not in that
community as close as you used to be
it's a different community
maybe you're not going to be as close
friendships but like this person is
is finding a way to like feel better and
i feel like
what you know any friends should be as
encouraging as they can like
after we had the conversation with mom
was kind of like yeah you know that is
that is true
uh it does open up it works for her like
she is happy
yeah so like what i should do is be
happy for her yep
yeah yeah not control her experience
yeah yeah and that's something else i
think that's hard because like we do
want to control people's experiences
because we think we can do it better
okay they're allowed to experience what
they're and that's so hard with
partnerships too i go through the same
thing i'm like
well if i was it was my shoes i would do
it this way and it would be but that's
not my it's not
my experience it's not his and vice
versa and i think when you are in
relationships people get so codependent
even though they don't even know what
that word means or i'm not codependent i
don't need them
but like when you're like basing off i
have some friends or
people that like won't make decisions
unless they talk to their partners first
which
that's fine that's on you but like i'm
not like that i'm very still
independently thinking
i trust my partner's opinion but like if
my partner's opinion was different than
mine i wouldn't like
not do what i wanted to do you know
thankfully my partner is very supportive
of me
but i feel like sometimes we have these
dreams and maybe our partners aren't
supporting it and it is blocking us um
so
sometimes you need to re-look at who you
tell your ideas to
also look at how are the people in your
life supporting your
crazy ideas because for a lot of my life
people in my life that i was closest to
wasn't supporting my unconventional
ideas and that's why i wasn't doing them
and then when i shifted in frequency
everyone in my life supports my dreams
yeah you start having people that come
around yeah everyone in my life is like
yeah reiki
like like yeah healing center like
everyone in my life is just so
supportive because they're at the same
frequency as me i dropped out other
people
you know who maybe were drinking more
than i like to drink or not doing the
work like i like to do the work you know
and spending their time differently than
me
um i just shifted it's not that i don't
i don't love those people it's not like
i'm not friends but
the vibration just didn't match anymore
yeah we have this like our
toxic thing of like cut them off if
they're this and like blah blah and like
it doesn't have to be like that it's
just like
i love you man but like i'm just going
over here like it's
it's here's what i want and
realistically in the end you find out
that
a lot of the people who do really love
you is they're like i don't know
anything about that stuff but i'm glad
you're happy man yeah because that's how
i feel like with a lot of my like older
friendships that's i feel that from them
it's like they're they're happy for
whatever i'm doing yeah
and that's the thing like to choose
people in your life though
that do support you and that's huge um
for me
if my the number one thing in my
relationship is that my partner supports
me spiritually
because spiritually is spirit is me i am
spirit
most of my life is spirit i'm tarot
cards i'm crystals i am smudge like
i mean i'm not i am not those things but
those are things that i do every day
i'm doing spirit i spiritually practice
every day something
you know so if i had a partner who was
constantly questioning my crystals
questioning my smudge
questioning me channeling questioning
what i was doing
i couldn't i wouldn't be able to do that
but since my partner allows me that
space i've just
amplified spiritually in my growth since
we've been together
because it's nice to have your partner
agree with you with spirit stuff
wow spiritually you agree like wow i'm
not crazy like oh cool like you think
this way too it's been so
such a blessing in my life to have my
partner support
me spiritually and to just be open to it
is the main thing i've never had him put
me down i've never had him question
my beliefs not that that's always a good
thing you know sometimes questioning
people's beliefs is
needed but it's so important for me to
have people in my life
who just allow me to be myself right
the way that we understand each other is
weird like sometimes we're like
hey don't you don't you go extending the
mold of the self
of you that i know like don't you go but
realistically it's like what you should
want out of your partner is just like
nothing but the most fulfilling life
like yeah you're together
but you're also here as two individual
humans and like
like you should be living the most
fulfilled life that you can
and and yeah encouragement definitely
helps with that
yeah and to also just with partners
because i'm really into like i'm with my
twin flame
um so basically we're the same person
and to realize that
your partner doesn't have to agree with
you though and to not be upset if they
don't agree with you
that's something that i'm going through
right now and to realize maybe our
values aren't the same but i love you
regardless how can we work on this
how can we meet in the middle oh i see
that this isn't as important to you as
it
is to me how can we meet in the middle
though because i don't want everything
that i want is important to be important
to you that's
that's unfair we grew up completely
different how can i expect you to have
the same
certainly life is me you know what i
mean so how can we meet in the middle
how can we like meld or mesh better what
can i do to be a better partner for you
well and that's always changing too yeah
that meeting in the middle is always
like
like it's wednesday and on tuesday it
was a different middle you kind of got
to flow with
life as it moves and to accept the
change and i think just in normal life
to allow change to happen
you know what i mean to allow when
opportunities happen and come up
crazy things and people give you crazy
opportunities just take it
so yes always say yes like going on a
podcast
like something that i like love doing
but it is like
you know for me to talk on here is
something it's forever
like who knows who can hear this and the
energy
i mean it's such a blessing that you're
doing this for people to speak it's like
a little therapy session to be heard and
for other people to hear you
yeah you know and to shift frequency
through voices and
beautiful gift yeah i love it i think
it's cool i feel like you uh
you were texting me because we had we
were working this around and
moving things around and stuff and
you're like i'm excited to see
how you've changed because i know that
i've changed and it was just it's just
cool to even notice
i guess i haven't listened back but like
just your confidence
in in this episode from from not that
you weren't confident in the last one
but just
um you know there's a familiarity of
like getting used to it's kind of this
weird thing with headphones and a
microphone and stuff but
the more you do it the more it's like oh
yeah this is okay i'm like oh yeah i do
believe this i'm just going to speak it
i'll have to plan it or i don't have to
right and to you know like because i'm
like the last time i go i want to talk
about this and i want to talk about that
but then today i was like
i'm just going to whatever you want to
talk about spirit like allow to flow
through me onto you into this microphone
i purposely have no notes here actually
that's a unusual thing for me really
usually because i wanted yeah i wanted
to i wanted to really be open to
experiencing the reiki experience
and then just really talk about that
that was my intention yeah
i don't know how long it's been but my
ears hurt but i want you to just
like if um if you could like explain
like your
experience like is this it was good yes
yeah it was good it was um i i enjoyed
it it's uh
i i can definitely tell that it's going
to come up
like i'm going to be thinking about it
more like i'm going to be like what what
is that about
um and i think
i think that it
it it was really cool to me i think
watching myself let's say
observing myself being so okay with it
and being so open for it is is so cool
to me because it's like
you're so ready for for whatever kind of
healing you're you really
are this person who wants to believe in
other people and
and uh experience life
to the to the to the fullest you know
seeing myself as someone who is so
willing
to allow allow allow you to perform like
this
you know different thing yeah um
energy work is crazy it's different it's
new we don't learn about it in school
our parents aren't getting it like it's
not something that we're really taught
about
so it is this alternative way of healing
but really it's so old
yeah it is and where i think we're
rediscovering it in a lot of ways and i
think it's very important
healers shamans or whatever healed with
their hands we didn't have hospitals
back then
hospital is a new thing you'd go to your
shaman
in your tribe you'd go to your medicine
woman you know and they would heal with
their hands
yeah i mean hospitals are great for like
your arms cut and yeah you got to get
it's great hospitals are great for me no
they are i love them thank you
but there are just alternative ways to
heal people yeah obviously when you're
in the hospital you've allowed it to get
way too far but energy work prevents
some of those physical things that could
happen
right because each chakra is associated
with an organ in your body
i can tell which organs people need help
with when i touch their bodies
i can see it i can see organs i can see
because i do know the anatomy
so i can like see the inside i can see
vessels that might have been a little
blocked or i can see nerves that might
not be connecting or
you know i'll be like oh did you have
this kind of injury you know oh did you
tear your
la i'll be really drawn and touching
people's knees
sometimes i'll be really drawn and
touching people's elbow you know just
their shoulder something on their
stomach it's something you know i'm
really drawn to doing that
i can't make this up you're not telling
me what you need i'm just intuitively i
can feel
like what i don't know how to explain it
it's just
again it's it's weird it's really hard
to describe
something you feel yes but i think it's
worth feeling and i think
it's worth letting down letting down
guards letting down
um remaining in disbelief these sort of
things i mean
i genuinely felt just equanimity at the
end of it i felt great like you
you you went to the other room and i was
just sitting here and like i couldn't
talk for
like five minutes really um it was just
very calming it was great i'm very
interested in it um
i i would love to experience it at some
point i would love to come up to your
location
yeah so um give everybody for listeners
give them how to get a hold of you again
um yeah
how to schedule an appointment all these
things i wish i was like way more
advanced in that way i am making a
website
um my company or my future wellness
center but i've just embodied it is
called a hizmagaya
and ahizma just means kind of like no
suffering
non-violence and gaia is the planet so
that's the name that i like didn't want
to share but i've had this name for a
while
and basically you can kind of like right
now it's just through instagram
um celestial gypsy witch but i will have
like a website
soon like i'm working on it i'm
struggling with it but then
also you know like if you just message
me
on instagram i can get there but i will
have like more advanced
things in the future i mean just because
you don't do things exactly how other
people do them like you're
you're honest about where you're at and
i think that's one of the best things i
think a lot of people will like that
even more like
i'm very like i'm you know i don't have
that website yeah booking
here online pay now it's very like
casual
that's perfect that's how we make
community yeah let's let's message each
other so
listener if you want to experience this
if you want to know more about it
get a hold of jay thank you celestial
gypsy witch on instagram yes
and then um
yeah thank you so much this was so great
yeah thank you i feel like lighter as
well
so it's like it's like i feel like
counseling it's like nice to just talk
about
things that matter it is it's great
thank you
yeah i appreciate you have a good day
listeners drink some water
junkyard love listeners please just get
present wherever you are get present use
all five of your senses just take a few
extra seconds a few extra minutes get
present look around you what's going on
what are you thinking about what are you
not thinking about
enjoy your life you're right here life
is right now
if you have a second before you move on
to whatever you're about to do
hit like hit subscribe follow
screen record send to a friend share
with somebody hit that little copy three
dots
send it to somebody say i like this
episode whatever
if you enjoyed it and if it helped you
share it
enjoy your day
you